(Amy:)Okay, I think I know
what to say now.
(Penny:)How can I not
sound like his mother
(Penny:)when our entire bedroom
is filled with Star Wars toys?
(Penny:)I mean, have you ever had sex
(Penny:)with a stuffed Wookiee
watching you?
I went to college in the '70s;
it was a hairier time.
(Dr Gallo:)I'm gonna say yes.
(Penny:)You know, if anything,
he's turning me into his mother.
(Penny:)Before I did pharmaceutical
sales, I was an actress.
(Penny:)You know, I was pretty good.
(Penny:)You know, girl-next-door type,
but hot.
(Penny:)Doable.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Penny:)And not only
am I Leonard's mother,
(Penny:)but we have this man-child
living with us named Sheldon.
(Dr Gallo:)Oh, Leonard talked a lot
about him.
(Dr Gallo:)I wasn't sure if he was real.
(Penny:)Yeah, he's as real
as the fine I get
(Penny:)when I use
too much toilet paper.
(Dr Gallo:)Wow, you really do have
a lot on your plate.
(Penny:)I do.
(Sheldon:)You know,
(Penny:)Leonard's right.
(Penny:)Talking to you
is really helping.
(Dr Gallo:)Oh, I'm glad.
(Dr Gallo:)You know, you might also benefit